**Warning**: getimagesize(): https:// wrapper is disabled in the server configuration by allow\_url\_fopen=0 in **/home/ehplusel/public\_html/templates/ehplus/index.php** on line **42**  
  
**Warning**: getimagesize(https://www.ehpluselectric.com/images/logos/ehplus-electric-logo-header-sm.png): Failed to open stream: no suitable wrapper could be found in **/home/ehplusel/public\_html/templates/ehplus/index.php** on line **42**  
  
**Warning**: Trying to access array offset on value of type bool in **/home/ehplusel/public\_html/templates/ehplus/index.php** on line **42**  
   Privacy Policy                            

======================================================================================================================================================================================================

[Products & Services](https://www.ehpluselectric.com/products-and-services)Toggle Dropdown

Client Links Toggle Dropdown

About Us Toggle Dropdown

Menu

* Client Links
* About Us

Powering great relationships, one customer at a time.

Get the Nest Thermostat installed by a Nest Certified Professional.

Some very god reasons to seek out an electrician.

Get the Nest Protect installed by a Nest Certified professional

Outdoor lighting is one of the easiest, most cost-effective ways to add beauty and security to your home.

1. You are here:  
2. [Home](https://www.ehpluselectric.com/) 
3. About Us 
4. Privacy Policy 

Privacy Policy
==============

Details

Category: [Uncategorised](https://www.ehpluselectric.com/about-us/privacy-policy?view=category&id=2)

Your privacy is critically important to us.

Eh Plus Electric Inc. is located at:  

PO Box 650  
Warburg, AB  
T0C 2T0, Canada  
+1 (855) 934-7587

It is Eh Plus Electric Inc.'s policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our website. This Privacy Policy applies to [https://www.ehpluselectric.com](https://www.ehpluselectric.com/) (hereinafter, "us", "we", or "https://www.ehpluselectric.com"). We respect your privacy and are committed to protecting personally identifiable information you may provide us through the Website. We have adopted this privacy policy ("Privacy Policy") to explain what information may be collected on our Website, how we use this information, and under what circumstances we may disclose the information to third parties. This Privacy Policy applies only to information we collect through the Website and does not apply to our collection of information from other sources.

This Privacy Policy, together with the Terms and conditions posted on our Website, set forth the general rules and policies governing your use of our Website. Depending on your activities when visiting our Website, you may be required to agree to additional terms and conditions.

Website Visitors
----------------

Like most website operators, Eh Plus Electric Inc. collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. Eh Plus Electric Inc.'s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how Eh Plus Electric Inc.'s visitors use its website. From time to time, Eh Plus Electric Inc. may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.

Eh Plus Electric Inc. also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses for logged in users and for users viewing and paying invoices in order to prevent fraudulent transactions and criminal activities.

Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information
-----------------------------------------------

Certain visitors to Eh Plus Electric Inc.'s websites choose to interact with Eh Plus Electric Inc. in ways that require Eh Plus Electric Inc. to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that Eh Plus Electric Inc. gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who are paying invoices on https://www.ehpluselectric.com to provide address and other contact information.

Security
--------

The security of your Personal Information is important to us, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

Links To External Sites
-----------------------

Our Service may contain links to external sites that are not operated by us. If you click on a third party link, you will be directed to that third party's site. We strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy and terms and conditions of every site you visit.

We have no control over, and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies or practices of any third party sites, products or services.

Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information
--------------------------------------------------------

Eh Plus Electric Inc. discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on Eh Plus Electric Inc.'s behalf or to provide services available at Eh Plus Electric Inc.'s website, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using Eh Plus Electric Inc.'s website, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. Eh Plus Electric Inc. will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, Eh Plus Electric Inc. discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only in response to a subpoena, court order or other governmental request, or when Eh Plus Electric Inc. believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of Eh Plus Electric Inc., third parties or the public at large.

Eh Plus Electric Inc. takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.

E-commerce
----------

Those who engage in transactions with Eh Plus Electric Inc. – by purchasing Eh Plus Electric Inc.'s services or products, are asked to provide additional information, including as necessary the personal and financial information required to process those transactions. In each case, Eh Plus Electric Inc. collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor's interaction with Eh Plus Electric Inc.. Eh Plus Electric Inc. does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.

Do Not Track
------------

Eh Plus Electric does not track users across third party websites to provide targeted advertising.

Privacy Policy Changes
----------------------

Although most changes are likely to be minor, Eh Plus Electric Inc. may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in Eh Plus Electric Inc.'s sole discretion. Eh Plus Electric Inc. encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.

Contact Information
-------------------

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us via This email address is being protected from spambots. You need JavaScript enabled to view it. or [phone](tel:18559347587).

Copyright © 2015-2024 Eh Plus Electric All rights reserved.
